Boya Wang
bw2462
Instructions:
Written1: I hardcoded the two lists in the program so you can just run the program directly without inputting anything.

Programming 1: Compile SymbolBalance, MyStack and Test. You need to put "Test.java" in the command line argument to run SymbolBalance.

Programming 2: Compile TwoStackQueue, MyQueue, and Program2. Run Program2 directly.

There's nothing I did differently from the instructions. 